<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Corey\'s Learn-athon</string>

    <string name="pyramid_string"> The Great Pyramid of Giza is the largest of all the Egyptian pyramids. The Great Pyramid was built as a tomb for the pharaoh Khufu. The pyramid once held all the treasures that Khufu would take with him to the afterlife. When the pyramid was built, it was around 481 feet tall. Today, because of erosion and the removal of the top piece, the pyramid is around 455 feet tall. At its base, each side is approximately 755 feet long. That\'s well over twice as long as a football field! It took 20,000 workers around 20 years to build the Great Pyramid. Its construction began around 2580 BC, shortly after Khufu became pharaoh, and was completed around 2560 BC.</string>
    <string name="greatwall_string"> The Great Wall of China is a wall that covers much of the northern border of China. The length of the Great Wall built by the Ming Dynasty is around 5,500 miles long. If you take the length of all the portions of the wall built by every Chinese Dynasty, plus various branches, the total comes to 13,171 miles long! No wonder they call it the Great Wall. The Great Wall of China is a wall that covers much of the northern border of China. The length of the Great Wall built by the Ming Dynasty is around 5,500 miles long. If you take the length of all the portions of the wall built by every Chinese Dynasty, plus various branches, the total comes to 13,171 miles long! No wonder they call it the Great Wall.</string>
    <string name="petra_string"> Petra (Batra in Arabic) was an ancient Arab city in what is now the southwestern part of Jordan. The modern town of Wadi Musa is located next to the site. The name Petra comes from the Greek word for “rock.” Many of Petra’s buildings were carved directly into rocky sandstone cliffs. Humans have lived in the area around Petra for tens of thousands of years. More than 2,000 years ago, an Arab tribe called the Nabataeans occupied Petra. The city grew very large. Between 10,000 and 30,000 people may have lived there. In AD106 the ancient Romans took over the Nabataean kingdom. Petra became a part of the Roman Empire.</string>
    <string name="colosseum_string"> Construction on the Colosseum was started in 72 AD by the emperor Vespasian. It was finished eight years later in 80 AD. The Colosseum was huge. It could seat 50,000 people. It covers around 6 acres of land and is 620 feet long, 512 feet wide, and 158 feet tall. It took more than 1.1 million tons of concrete, stone, and bricks to complete the Colosseum. Where people sat in the Colosseum was determined by Roman law. The best seats were reserved for the Senators. Behind them were the equestrians or ranking government officials. A bit higher up sat the ordinary Roman citizens (men) and the soldiers. Finally, at the top of the stadium sat the slaves and the women.</string>
    <string name="chichen_string"> The city of Chichén Itzá was once a center of culture and religion for the Maya people. Today the ruins of the city are a major archaeological site. They are located on the Yucatán Peninsula in southern Mexico. The city’s name comes partly from two big cenotes, or wells, on the site. Chi means “mouths,” chen means “wells,” and Itzá is the name of one Maya tribe that settled there. The city was founded in about the 500s ce by Maya people who may have come from the lowlands of the Yucatán. In about 1000 the city was invaded by foreigners. These may have been Mayan-speaking people from central Mexico. The invaders made Chichén Itzá their capital and built many new structures.</string>
    <string name="machu_string"> In the mountains of south-central Peru stands Machu Picchu, a deserted city of the Inca people. The name Machu Picchu means “old peak” in Quechua, the language of the Inca. The dwellings at the site were probably built and occupied from the mid-1400s to the early or mid-1500s. It lies between two sharp peaks in the eastern Andes Mountains, at a height of 7,710 feet. Machu Picchu is divided into two sections, one farming and one urban. The farming section is made up of steplike fields called terraces. The urban section has plazas, temples, houses, and a cemetery. They are connected by walkways and thousands of stone steps.</string>
    <string name="taj_string"> The Taj Mahal is considered one of the most beautiful buildings in the world. It is located in the city of Agra in northern India. A ruler named Shah Jahan had the Taj Mahal built as a monument and tomb for his beloved wife, Mumtaz Mahal. Shah Jahan was the Muslim ruler of the Mughal Empire in India from 1628 to 1658. His wife died in 1631, and the construction of the Taj Mahal began the following year. The monument is located on the bank of the Yamuna River. It is surrounded by formal gardens and reflecting ponds. The building rests on a square marble base that rises 23 feet high. Pure white marble covers the outside of the building.</string>
    <string name="christ_string"> At the top of Mount Corcovado in southeastern Brazil, overlooking Rio de Janeiro, stands a colossal statue of Jesus Christ called Christ the Redeemer. It is the largest Art Deco-style sculpture in the world and is one of Rio de Janeiro’s most recognizable landmarks. Construction began on the statue in 1926 and was completed five years later. The statue stands 98 feet tall, and its horizontally outstretched arms span 92 feet (28 meters). It is made of reinforced concrete clad in a mosaic of thousands of triangular soapstone tiles. The square stone pedestal base upon which the statue rests is about 26 feet high.</string>

    <string name="prompt"> Select one of the options below to learn more!</string>
    <string name="locButton">Open Location</string>
    <string name="continueButton">Continue to Corey\'s Learn-athon!</string>
    <string name="linkMessage">Click me to learn more!</string>
</resources>